#### Ms. CHAITANYA R KURUP

Email address: <a href="mailto:ckurup96@gmail.com">ckurup96@gmail.com</a>

Mobile Number: 9167875641

3 Years of experience in banking and insurance as junior officer, customer service executive and process associate

## **Profile:**

Being into insurance and banking operations for 3 years with organizations like Saraswat cooperative bank, India First Life Insurance Corporation Ltd and TCS. I have gathered potential knowledge in different areas of banking and insurance by working as customer service executive and junior officer in different departments like Deposits and loan department.

To work for a challenging and rewarding opportunity in an organization wherein, I could get more exposure on my career and I can utilize my skills and knowledge which will contribute towards organization's growth.

#### **Target Position:**

Target industry: Retail Banking, Corporate Banking and Insurance

## **Professional Experience**

Saraswat co-operative bank: October 2021 to Till Date

**Department**: Branch operation

**Designation**: Junior Officer

- NEFT, RTGS and clearing cheques after clear scrutiny and authorization of the required documents.
- Modifications in customer's account in finacle as per request
- KYC updation of customer as and when requirements are raised by the RBI.
- Handlings queries at customer facing counter and mail processing
- Handled Demat department with market, off-market and inter depository slip processing and handling various demat related queries.
- Worked with loan department and deposits sections.
- Customer account verification with regards to Debit/Credit happen in accounts
- Daily reports analysis

India First Life Insurance Company Pvt Ltd: August 2018 to April 2020

**Department**: Operations

**Designation:** Customer Service Executive

- Helping customers to know about their Insurance policies and processes as per IRDAI guidelines.
- Handlings queries and mail processing.
- Making changes in the policy as per customer's request.
- Maintaining good customer service of the company.
- Retention of customer, willing to cancel the policy with complete satisfaction of customer.
- Follow up with customers.
- Converting leads

TATA Consultancy Services PVT Ltd: June 2017 to March 2018

**Department:** Business process Solutions

**Designation:** Process Associate

- Assigned and performed role of information process specialist, which includes managing Institutional corporate client group (ICCG) customers.
- Customer account verification with regards to Debit/Credit happen in accounts.
- Handling FIRC i.e. foreign inward remittance certificate and issuance of the same inconnecting with RBI guidelines.
- Handlings queries and mail processing.
- Follow up with customers and relationship manager.
- Daily transaction reporting

## **Education:**

Masters in Commerce from Mumbai University July 2017-March 2019

Bachelors Of Commerce- Mumbai University – July 2014 to March 2017

Plus two- Higher Secondary Board of Maharashtra-July 2012 to March 2017

SSLC- SSLC Board of Maharashtra- 2012

# **Personal Information:**

Birth Date: 19 November. 1996

Nationality: Indian

Marital Status: Unmarried

Residence: Mira Road.

I hearby declare that the above information is best of my knowledge.

Chaitanya Kurup.